乔伊 试镜情况如何     非常好
Hey Joey, how'd the audition go?        Incredible.
这回我见到导演了
I met the director this time.
而你们绝对想不到会是谁
And you'll never believe who it was.
谁
Who?
好吧 给你们一条提示
All right. I'll give you one hint.
沃伦・比蒂
Warren Beatty.
哇
Wow!
但有件事情可能会成为小问题
Yeah, there's just one thing that might be kind of a problem. See...
我必须亲一个男人
I had to kiss this guy.
因为他帅得要命
Because he was just so darn cute?
不是 是试镜的一部分
No, as part of the audition.
我试镜的角色是 男主角要亲的男人
See, I'm up for this part of this guy who the main guy kisses.
嘿 你是个演员 要我说你就认命吧 亲呗
Well, hey. You're an actor, I say you just suck it up and you do it.
或是你就吻好了
Or you just do it.
我吻了 我很专业的
I did do it. I'm a professional.
那还有什么问题
So, what's the problem?
那场戏拍完之后 比蒂先生走过来跟我说
See, after the scene, Mr. Beatty comes up to me and says
"好演技 差吻技"
"good actor, bad kisser"
你能相信吗 说我吻技差
Can you believe that? Me, not a good kisser.
这就像是说
That's like, like...
特蕾莎修女不是个好修女
Mother Teresa, not a good mother.
拜托 谁在乎那个家伙怎么想
Well, come on, who cares what that guy thinks, you know?
沃伦・比蒂哪懂什么叫接吻
What does Warren Beatty know about kissing?
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧
《老友记》蓝光版 第02季 第24集（季终集）
巴瑞和敏蒂的婚礼 Barry and Mindy's Wedding
调校制作：寒 枫
字幕编辑：小龟快快跑
嘿 你的经纪人怎么说
Hey, what did your agent say?
接吻这件事绝对是个问题
Yep. This kiss thing is definitely a problem.
比蒂先生周一要再看一次
Mr. Beatty wants to see it again on Monday.
老天 我必须得搞清楚 问题到底出在哪儿
Man, I gotta figure out what I'm doing wrong.
好吧 你们哪个女生过来吻我
Oh, okay. One of you girls come over here and kiss me.
休想      想得真美
Forget it.        Yeah, right.
拜托 我需要帮助
Hey, come on. I need your help here.
好吧 我来
All right. I'll do it.
我以前吻过他 再来一次也行
I kissed him before. I can do it again.
看到没 这才叫朋友
See this, huh? This is a friend.
来吧
Uh-huh. Let's go.
等一下 口香糖还在嘴里
Oh, wait. I have gum.
好了
Okay.
好 非常好 坚定又不失温柔
Good. Very good. Firm, but tender.
我会跟朋友推荐你
I'd recommend you to a friend.
那我就不知道问题到底在哪儿了 到底哪儿不对了
Then I don't know what it is. What's the problem?
乔伊 或许你只是不习惯吻男人
Joey, you know, maybe you're just not used to kissing men.
也许你只是有点小紧张
You know? Maybe you just tensed up a little bit.
也许你要克服这一点
Maybe that's what you need to work on.
对呀 说得有理
Yeah, that makes sense.
除非我死了
Over my dead body.
我会用他的尸体当盾牌
And I'll be using his dead body as a shield.
出来吧 亲爱的 你看起来美极了
Come on out, honey! I'm telling you, you look good!
说她美极了 说她美极了
Tell her she looks good. Tell her she looks good.
我的天哪
Oh my God!
你好美喔
You look so good!
我真不敢相信自己 要在两百人面前走上红毯
I cannot believe I have to walk down the aisle in front of 200 people,
而自己打扮得却像是 别人恶心想吐时喝的药水
looking like something you drink when you're nauseous.
那就别去了 搞不懂我们为什么非去不可
So don't. I don't see why we have to go to this thing anyway.
反正是你前未婚夫的婚礼
It's your ex-fiancee's wedding.
因为我答应了敏蒂会去的
Because I promised Mindy I would.
你还答应巴瑞说会嫁给他呢
Yeah well, you promised Barry you'd marry him.
各位 我必须去 我是伴娘
You guys, I have to go. I'm the maid of honor.
除此之外
And besides you know what?
我只是需要跟这些人再聚首时
I just need to be in a room again with these people...
对自己更有信心一点
and feel good about myself.
有人今天穿的还是昨天那身衣服
Someone's wearing the same clothes they had on last night.
看来有人有艳遇哦
Someone get a little action?
没错 有这个可能
Yeah, I may have.
不错嘛 欲望小子
Whoo-hoo! Stud!
她长什么样子
What's she look like?
我们还没见过面呢
Well, we haven't actually met.
我们只是整晚在网上聊天
We just stayed up all night talking on the internet.
呜呼 怪胎
Whoo-hoo! Geek!
我喜欢她 我真的喜欢她
I like this girl, okay, I seriously like this girl.
你们也知道 有时候我会有点自我保护和爱讽刺人
You know how sometimes I tend get a little defended and quipy?
哪有      没有
Get out.        No. Please.
她很直接揭穿我
Well, she totally called me on it, okay?
她说 省省吧 正经点儿
She said "Cut it out, get real."
于是我照做了
And I did.
哇
Wow!
那是什么样子
What's that like?
就像这样 我
It's like this, me.
不嬉皮笑脸
No jokes.
好吧 别这样 你吓到我了
All right, stop it, you're freaking me out.
没错 我不喜欢你这个样子
Oh, yeah, I don't like you this way.
好了 晚点儿再见了
All right, I'll see you guys later.
再见 理查      再见
Bye, Richard.        Bye-bye.
再见 甜心 我爱你
Bye, sweetie. I love you.
我也爱你
I love you too.
我觉得我男朋友好棒哦
I think my boyfriend ever so dreamy.
我想知道我的婚礼会是什么样的
I wonder what our wedding's gonna be like.
说什么呢 什么婚礼
What are you talking about? What wedding?
少来 像是你们从没讨论过似的
Come on, like you never talk that?
没有 从来没有
No! Never!
我们只是享受当下
I mean, we're just living in the moment.
就这么一次 感觉好极了
God, it is so nice for once to not have to get all
不用老想着"将来会怎么样"
hung up on "Where is this going?"
害怕问他吧      怕得要命
Afraid to ask him?        Could not be more terrified.
我认为你们应该认真地考虑一下结婚这件事
Well, I think you should seriously consider the marriage thing.
再给瑞秋一次当泡泡糖公主的机会
Give Rachel another chance to dress up like Princess "Bubble Yum".
小本在哪儿呢
Where's Benny?
在这儿呢
There he is.
小本在哪儿呢
Where's Benny?
在这儿呢
There he is!
这大概就是小宝宝要学说话的原因
You know, that's probably why babies learn to talk.
是要叫大人闭嘴
So they can tell grownups to cut it out.
有个问题想问你
Hey, you know I got a question for you.
小事而已 别有压力
Just a little thing, no pressure.
好
Okay!
你有没有想过将来
Do you ever, uh, like think about the future?
当然想过
Sure I do.
是吗
Yeah?
有我吗
Am I in it?
亲爱的
Honey,
你就是我的将来
you are it.
老天 你走大运了
Oh God! You're about to get so lucky.
没错
Yeah!
接着说      这个嘛
Keep talking.        Well...
有时候 我想过要卖掉诊所
Sometimes I think about selling my practice.
我们可以搬去法国
We could move to France.
做法式吐司
Make French toast.
这么说
Okay, so...
我们在法国
we're in France and...
我们做吐司
we're making the toast.
你有没有在角落里看到个小摇篮
Do you see a little bassinet in the corner?
像个狗窝吗
Like a hound?
不是狗
Not a basset.
是婴儿摇篮
A bassinet.
你真想要个婴儿摇篮
You really need the bassinet?
我只是觉得 宝宝会从狗身上掉下来呀
Well, I just think the baby would keep falling off the dog.
我们的未来里 难道没有小孩吗
Do you, uh, do you , do you not see kids in our future?
噢 嘿
Oh! Hey!
我爱孩子
I love children.
我有孩子
I have children.
我只是不想等到七十岁 我们的孩子才刚上大学
But I just don't want to be seventy when our kids go off to college...
然后我们才开始自己的生活
And our life can finally start.
听着
Look,
我要你
I want you...
就现在
now.
这样很好
That's great.
其实也不用现在讨论这种事
You know we don't need to talk about this now.
真的 这是许久许久以后的事
Really. I mean, this is so, like, way way way in the future.
远得像是猿人接管了地球以后的事
I'm talking hovercrafts and apes taking over the planet.
拜托 钱德 我真的很想得到这个角色
Come on, Chandler. I want this part so much.
只是一个吻而已 我不会告诉别人的
Just one kiss. I won't tell anyone.
乔伊 不行就是不行
Joey, no means no.
嘿
Hey!
不好意思 你的羊不在我们这里
I'm sorry, we don't have your sheep.
瑞秋 我觉得你看起来很可爱
Aw, Rach, I think you look cute.
而你 你
And you. You...
我真想咬你一口
You, I could eat you with a spoon.
离我远一点 说了不行了
Get away from me. I said no.
理查按门铃了 他在楼下等着
Richard buzzed. He's waiting downstairs.
理查来了
Richard's here?
我应该下去 跟他道个别
I should run down, say goodbye to him.
再见      祝你们好运
Bye.        Good luck.
你跟你的网络女友怎么样了
So, how's your date with your cyber-chick going?
那是什么
Ooh, hey, what is all that?
古根海姆博物馆的网站
Oh, it's a web site. It's the Guggenheim Museum.
她喜欢艺术
See, she likes art and...
我喜欢滑稽的字眼
I like funny words.
"握握"是什么意思
What does she mean by "HH"?
表示我们手牵着手
It means we're holding hands.
你真是太可爱了
Are you the cutest?
你说对了
I'm afraid I might just be.
你知道我觉得最棒的地方是什么吗
You know, what I think is so great that
你完全被这个人迷住了
you are totally into this person.
但你却又知道她可能
And yet for all you know she could be like...
90岁或是有两个脑袋 又或是
ninety years old, or have two heads or...
根本就是个男人
It could be a guy.
不是个男人 好不好 我了解她
Okay, it's not a guy, all right? I know her.
有可能是个大块头的男人
It could be like a big, giant guy.
可恶 就差那么一点点
Man, I got this close to him.
摩妮卡从后面踹了我一脚
And Monica kneed me in the back.
你们在干嘛
What's going on?
我们在猜 钱德的女友是不是女生
We're wondering if Chandler's girlfriend is a girl.
那就问问她 她会活多久
Oh, well. Just ask her how long she's gonna live.
女人比男人长寿
Women live longer than men.
你怎么没多摔两跤
How do you not fall down more?
这样好了 问她怎么避孕
Okay, ask her what is her method of birth control.
好吧
All right.
我老公跟他的秘书乱搞
"My husband is sleeping with his secretary."
她结婚了
She's married?
至少我们确定她是女人了
At least we know she's a woman.
真不敢相信她结婚了
I can't believe she's married.
兄弟 我很遗憾
Oh, man, I'm sorry.
你一定很难过
This must be really tough for you.
我那天看过一篇文章
So, I read this article in the paper the other day,
上面说婚礼上不该撒米
that says you're not supposed to throw rice at weddings.
因为鸽子吃米会死
Because when pigeons eat rice, it kills them.
难怪你不可能在寿司店看到鸽子
Oh, that's why you never see pigeons at sushi bars.
瞧 我们这不是很开心吗      当然
See, we're having fun.        Oh, absolutely.
我甚至都没在想 我们不该想的那件事
Yeah, you know, I'm not even thinking about that thing that we're not gonna think about.
我也是
Neither am I.
嗨      嗨
Hey, there.        Hi!
你还好吗
Are you all right?
还好
Yeah.
我去洗手间的时候
But when I was in the bathroom
看到我结婚时爬出去的那扇窗子
I saw the window that I crawled out of at my wedding. And...
天啊 我开始觉得自己真不该来 不该来
God! I just started thinking that I shouldn't be here, you know? I shouldn't.
大家会看着我
People are gonna be looking at me
对我评头论足  还会想到上一次的事
and judging me and, and thinking about the last time...
亲爱的 不会有事的 这是个婚礼
Sweetie, it's gonna be okay, all right? It's a wedding.
一般来说 大家的焦点都在新娘身上
Generally, people focus on the bride.
我知道 你说的对
God! I know. You're right.
好了 大家都看我 很好 是时候了
Alright. Everybody look at me. Good. All right, it's time.
伴娘和迎宾员 请站成两列 谢谢
Bridesmaids and ushers, let's see two lines. Thank you.
仪式结束后见
Okay. I'll  see you after the thing.
好 祝你好运      谢谢 好啦
Okay. Good luck.        Thank you. Okay.
好啦
Okay!
你为什么不告诉我
Why the hell didn't you tell me!
对不起 我不知道应该怎么做
I'm sorry. What was I supposed to do?
站起来大喊 瑞秋 你的屁股露出来了
Stand up and shout, "Hey, Rachel, your butt is showing!"
天哪 丢死人了
Oh my God! This is so humiliating.
我想唯一比这个还要丢脸的是  八年级时
I think the only thing that tops that was, was, was when I was in the eight grade...
在全校面前唱"科巴卡巴那"
and I had to sing the"Copacabana" in front of the entire school.
我大概还没唱两句就被吓得逃之夭夭了
I think I got about two lines into it before I ran and freaked out..
我的天啊 我的人生在我眼前闪过
Oh my God! My entire life is flashing before my eyes.
瑞秋 我记得那一次 其实也没那么糟
Rach, hey look, I remember that. It wasn't so bad.
罗斯 你不用说好话给我听了 你已经追到我了
Oh Ross, would you stop? You got me. I'm dating you.
瑞秋
Rachel.
嗨 温伯格先生 嗨 温伯格太太
Hi, Mr. Weinberg. Hi, Mrs. Weinberg.
很高兴又见到你了 亲爱的
It's so wonderful to see you again, my dear.
老实说 我没想到会看到那么多
In fact, I hardly expected to see so much.
你说你什么都没看到的
You told me you didn't see anything.
我跟你说的话多得去了
I tell you a lot of things.
真高兴又看到你出来走动了 亲爱的
Well, it's wonderful to have you up and about again, dear.
好好照顾自己
Stay well.
类似刚刚那种话 我今天已经听到三次了
Okay, now that is the third time someone has said something like that to me today.
瑞秋 瑞秋       嗨
Rach! Rach!        Oh! Hi!
我的天啊 我结婚了      对啊
Oh my God, I'm married!        I know!
我是巴瑞・亨特・法巴尔夫人
I'm Mrs. Dr. Barry Hunter-Farber.
我真以你为荣 敏
I am so proud of you, Min.
敏
Min.
瑞秋 你还在啊
Oh, Rach. Still here.
我们婚礼的这个时候 他们已经在打包收盘子了
At our wedding, they were packing up the chopped liver about now.
是呀 有趣的故事
Yeah, I love that story.
我有个问题要问你们
I have a question for you guys.
为什么大家一直说 很高兴看到我出来走动
Why do people keep saying it's good to see me up and about?
你逃婚后
Well, after you ran out on your wedding,
巴瑞的父母跟大家说你
Barry's parents told people you were sort of...
疯了
insane.
Insane?
因为得了梅毒
From the syphilis.
什么
What?
对
Yeah!
不然你要他们怎么说 说你不爱我了 怎么可能
What are they gonna say? You didn't love me anymore? Come on.
安琪拉
Angela?
乔伊・崔比亚尼
Joey Tribbiani.
是这样
Listen...
你今晚有事吗
what are you doing tonight?
我知道你在跟那个家伙交往
I know you're seeing that guy.
我在想或许你可以带他来
I was thinking maybe you could bring him...
喂 喂
Hello? Hello!
你不打算回她吗
Aren't you gonna answer her?
她已经叮咚你第十次了
That's like the tenth bing-bong message she sent.
她想知道怎么了
She wants to know what's wrong.
怎么了 怎么了 你结婚了 这就是怎么了
What's wrong? What's wrong? You're married! That's what's wrong!
天啊
Oh, my!
怎么了
What?
她想跟你见面
She wants to meet you in person.
菲比 我也想见她
Hey, look, Phoebe, I wanted to meet her in person too. Okay?
但是她结婚了 她有老公
But she's married. She has a husband.
如果她的老公注定是个错误
What if the husband person is the wrong guy.
而你却是真命天子呢
And you are the right guy?
这种机会不常有的
You don't get chances like this all the time.
如果你现在不见她 到八十岁时 你会气得踢自己
If you don't meet her now, you're gonna be kicking yourself when you're eighty...
这个动作难度很高 你可能因此摔坏屁股
which is hard to do, and that's how you break a hip.
好吧 我去见她
Okay. I'll do it.
太好了 太好了
Oh, yeah! Okay! Great!
快穿上鞋 然后走出去见她
Go, man, go put on your shoes and march out there and meet her!
等等 天哪 你得先洗个澡 不然很臭
Oh, wait! God! No! Wait, you've got to take a shower because ew!
而我要
And I'll get the...
不对 你应该先回她 先回她
No! You have to answer her, answer her first.
不 不 你先煮咖啡 因为压力太大了
No, no, you know what? Make some coffee because it's too much.
再来一次 求你了
Okay, one more, please.
来嘛 这次一定行 一定
Come on, I'm gonna get it in this time, I will.
好吧 最后一次
Okay, last chance.
再一次 对不起
Again, I'm sorry.
知道吗
You know what?
或许我不需要有孩子
Maybe I don't need to have children.
也许我之所以认为我需要 是因为这个社会
You know, maybe I just think I do because that is what society.
我说的社会就是指我妈
And by that I mean my mom,
老是向我灌输 说我
has always convinced me that I...
我要
I do.
我必须得有孩子 很抱歉 我就是想要
I have to have children. I'm sorry. I just do.
各位看这里可以吗
Yo! Can I have your attention, please!
伴郎要敬酒了
Best man making a toast here.
谢谢
Thank you.
我记得巴瑞第一次跟瑞秋约会回来的时候
I remember when Barry got home from his first date with Rachel.
干嘛
What?
你请了同一个乐队 我就不能用同一个演讲稿
You hired the same band. I can't use the same speech?
谢谢 非常感谢
Thank you. Thank you very much.
总之 我希望你们两个
Anyway, I wish you both...
幸福美满地生活在一起
a wonderful life together.
瑞秋
And Rachel.
干嘛      不 不 不 我是非常认真的
What?        No, no, no, now in all seriousness.
没有多少女人有这个胆子 敢在今晚回来这里
It's not a lot of women would've had the guts to come back here tonight.
更别说是光着屁股回来
And even fewer who would do it with their asses hanging out!
就这些了
That's it.
我想补充两句
I'd like to add something to that.
你要补充什么      没事的 没事的
What are you adding?        It's okay. It's okay.
多数人还不认识我
Most of you don't know me.
我是瑞秋的男朋友
I'm Rachel's boyfriend.
我的老天爷啊
Oh, dear God!
罗斯
Ross.
我想说的是
And I'd just like to say that...
瑞秋今晚能回来这里 的确是鼓起了很大的勇气
it did take a lot of courage for Rachel to come here tonight.
而且我要郑重声明
And just for the record,
她不是因为梅毒才悔婚的
she did not run out on Barry because she had syphilis.
你们干嘛呢 我是认真的
What are you doing? I'm serious.
之所以
The reason...
瑞秋会离开巴瑞 只是因为
she walked out on Barry is simply that...
她不爱他
she didn't love him.
因此意外地成全了我的美事
Which, incidentally, worked out pretty well for me.
干杯
Cheers.
我在停车场等你      别 瑞秋
See you in the parking lot.        No, Rach!
她再一次离开了
And once again, she is out of here!
谁赌了9点45分
Okay, who had 9:45?
你知道吗 巴瑞
You know what, Bar?
我不会走
I'm not gonna leave.
可能我应该走 但是我不走
I probably should, but I'm not.
因为我答应自己 至少要过完一次你的婚礼
See 'cause I promised myself that I would make it through at least one of your weddings.
我今天想要的只不过是
See now, tonight, all I really wanted was
一点优雅跟尊严 来撑过今晚
to make it though this evening with a little bit of grace and dignity.
我猜
Well, I guess...
大家也都认同 这种事是不可能发生的
we can all agree that's not gonna happen.
我猜  也没什么可多说的
I guess there's nothing really left to say...
除了
except...
她的名字叫萝拉
Her name was Lola.
她是歌舞女郎
She was a showgirl.
挂着黄色羽毛
With yellow feather...
头发上挂着羽毛
Feathers in her hair.
还有短到不行的裙子
And a dress cut down to there.
她会
She would...
梅伦格舞      梅伦格舞
Merengue.        Merengue.
谢谢你 亲爱的
Thank you, honey.
还会跳恰恰
And do the cha-cha.
她喜欢当明星的滋味 而托尼则是酒保
And while she'd like to be a star. Tony always tended bar.
等等
Wait, wait!
大家一起来
Everybody!
科巴卡巴那
Copacabana.
是哈瓦那北部最带劲的地方
The hottest spot north of Havana.
在科巴
At the Copa.
科巴卡巴那
Copacabana.
音乐与热情永远是科巴的主旋律
Music and passion were always in fashion at the Copa.
好吧
Okay.
我愿意
I'll do it.
愿意什么
You'll do what?
如果非得要孩子才能跟你在一起 那就生孩子吧
If kids is what it takes to be with you, then kids it is.
我的天啊
Oh my God.
如果非得这样 我可以重来一遍
If I have to, I'll do it all again.
我会早上四点起来喂奶
I'll do the 4 o'clock feeding thing.
我会去参加家长会
I'll go to the P.T.A. meetings.
我会当足球队教练
I'll coach the soccer team.
真的吗      没错 非得这样的话
Really?        Yeah, if I have to.
摩妮卡
Monica...
我不想失去你
I don't wanna lose you.
如果一定要重来一遍
So, if I have to do it all again,
那我愿意
then I will.
你是我见过的最棒的男人
You are the most wonderful man.
如果你没说那么多次
And if you hadn't of said...
"非得不可的话"
"If I have to", like seventeen times...
我一定会说 "好吧 我们生吧"
then I'd be saying "okay, let's do it."
但是你没有
But you're not.
天啊
Oh my God!
真不敢相信我就要这么说了
I can't believe what I'm getting ready to say.
我想要孩子
I wanna have a baby.
但我不想跟一个 并不真的想要孩子的人一起生
But I don't wanna have one with someone who doesn't really wanna have one.
天啊
God.
我爱你
I love you.
我知道
I know you do.
我也是
Me too.
那现在怎么办
So what now?
我们就
I guess we just...
一直跳下去
keep dancing.
她在哪儿 她在哪儿
Where is she? Where is she?
嘿 我有个问题
Oh, hey, I have a question.
她在哪儿
Where is she?
钱德 淡定 她会来的
Chandler, relax, Chandler. She'll be here.
她来了
Oh, oh, oh. That's her.
是啊 因为人生就是这么美好
Yeah, because life's just that kind.
钱德 别再盯着门看了
Chandler, you gotta stop staring at the door.
就像一个被盯着看的水壶
It's like a watched pot.
如果你一直盯着看 门永远不会开
You know, if you keep looking at it, the door's never gonna boil.
你必须试着不要去
I think what you have to do is try not to...
我的天
Oh my God!
我
Oh!
的
My!
天
God!
我
Oh!
的
My!
天
God!
好吧
All right.
我一直觉得非常内疚
I've been feeling incredibly guilty,
因为我想当个好朋友
because I wanna be a good friend.
该死 我是个好朋友
And damn it, I am a good friend.
所以 闭上嘴 闭上眼睛
So shut up and close your eyes.
你是个好朋友
You are a good friend.
试镜是今天早上 而我出局了
The audition was this morning, and I didn't get it.
但是这个吻很不错
But that was a hell of a kiss.
瑞秋很幸运
Rachel is a very lucky girl.
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧